- 你在干嘛呢  - 噢
- Whatcha doing? - Ooh!
别这么偷偷靠近我
Do not sneak up on me like that.
你在维罗的储物柜前干什么呢
What are you doing at Willow's locker?
更重要的是  我在维罗的储物柜前干什么呢
More importantly, what am I doing at Willow's locker?
那是一张留言条吗
Is that a note?
对  你千万别和任何人说
Yeah, actually, don't tell anyone,
但是我在帮我们俩一个忙
but I'm doing us both a favor.
这是一封匿名的情书
It's a secret admirer note
来帮维罗移情别恋
to get Willow to stop obsessing about you.
我希望你写好点
I hope you wrote a good one.
维罗犯的乔伊病已经病入膏肓了
Willow's got a bad case of the Joeys,
我还不确定有药能治好
and I'm not sure there's a cure.
唔  我脖子后边的汗毛立起来了
Hmm, the hairs on the back of my neck just stood up.
维罗要来了 快跑
Willow's coming. Run.
乔伊你好啊
Hey, Joey.
美女你好啊
Hey, beautiful.
这是什么
What's this?
有人喜欢我
Secret admirer?
哦不  不会吧
Oh-ho. No way.
看起来她相信了
It looks like she's buying it.
别学我这么站
Stop standing like me.
我们长得又不像
We do not look alike.